{
    "id": "f5356afe5b2a4c07825e605f8b1cf7fa",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Are you going to …………………. with your cousin while you are in Sydney?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get in touch",
                "getting in touch",
                "have in touch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db1f35448366489c8501bfbfb310caca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her hands were ………………. with cold when we found her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blue",
                "red",
                "green"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee6066011a62439881d10a8b4ea80389"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is John ………………… the phone. He wants to talk to you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbd486dc7dcb4057af23ce6df72601c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must ………………. your plans before we go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "discuss",
                "discuss after",
                "discuss about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd8d3b381a434227b0b4506d45e9216c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which flight is she traveling …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc77878e47c1468fad1e7cde21f61387"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. them since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "have known",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4120e5b6ae14c7681aa631d195f7105"
        },
        {
            "question": "Heat ………………….. bodies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is expanding",
                "expands",
                "expand",
                "has expanded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4105ebda1b2e48b9b6039fd5a658d894"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kettle ………………… Shall I make tree?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boils",
                "is boiling",
                "has boiled",
                "has been boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf3590e95c304ed5ad0a08ffa1e991f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t have any parcels for you today. I ..................... tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have any",
                "may have some",
                "may have any",
                "have some"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa1a397494c74f2484770b3eb5cf1726"
        },
        {
            "question": "Merchant of Venice is one of Shakespeare’s early ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plays",
                "play",
                "drama",
                "dramas"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6eb1f4c64774901933a4547991c3445"
        }
    ]
}